<xml>
    <metaData>
        <title>get him back!</title>
        <doc type="lyrics">Lyrics</doc>
        <artist persName="oliviaR"/>
        <album>GUTS</album>
        <!--persName="alex23"-->
    </metaData>

    <intro persName="alex23">
        <p>One, two, three</p>
        <p>Wait, is this the song with the drums?</p>
    </intro>

    <verse n="1" rhyme="aabbccddeeff">
        <p>I met a guy in the summer, and I left him in the spring</p>
        <p>He argued with me about everything</p>
        <p>He had an ego and a temper and a <figlang type="meta">wandering eye</figlang></p>
        <p>He said he's six-foot-two, and I'm like, <format type="q">Dude, nice try</format></p>
        <p>But he was so much fun, and he had such weird friends</p>
        <p>And he would take us out to parties, and <figlang type="hyper">the night would never
                end</figlang></p>
        <p>Another song, another club, another bar, another dance</p>
        <p>And when hе said something wrong, he'd just fly me to Francе</p>
        <p>So I miss him some nights when I'm feeling depressed</p>
        <p>'Til I remember every time <figlang type="euph">he made a pass on my friend</figlang></p>
        <p>Do I love him? Do I hate him? I guess it's up and down</p>
        <p>If I had to choose, I would say right now</p>
    </verse>

    <chorus rhyme="ababcad">
        <p>I wanna get him back</p>
        <p>I wanna make him really jealous, wanna make him feel bad</p>
        <p>Oh, I wanna get him back</p>
        <p>'Cause then again, I really miss him, and it makes me real sad</p>
        <p>Oh, I want sweet revenge, and I want him again</p>
        <p>I want to get him back, back, back</p>
    </chorus>

    <verse n="2" rhyme="aabbccdd">
        <p>So I write him all these letters, and I throw them in the trash</p>
        <p>'Cause I miss the way he kisses and the way he made me laugh</p>
        <p>Yeah, <figlang type="meta">I pour my little heart out</figlang>, but as I'm hitting
                <format type="q">send</format></p>
        <p>
            <figlang type="image">I picture all the faces of my disappointed friends</figlang>
        </p>
        <p>Because everyone knew all of the shit that he'd do</p>
        <p>He said I was the only girl, but that just wasn't the truth</p>
        <p>And when I told him how he hurt me, he'd tell me I was trippin'</p>
        <p>But I am my father's daughter, so maybe <figlang type="meta">I could fix
            him</figlang></p>
    </verse>

    <chorus rhyme="ababcaa">
        <p>I wanna get him back</p>
        <p>I wanna make him really jealous, wanna make him feel bad</p>
        <p>Oh, I wanna get him back</p>
        <p>'Cause then again, I really miss him, and it makes me real sad</p>
        <p>Oh, I want sweet revenge, and I want him again</p>
        <p>I want to get him back <format type="p">And then? And then</format></p>
        <p>I want to get him back, back, back</p>
    </chorus>

    <bridge persName="oliviaR" rhyme="ababcdedbbdd">
        <!--ask dr b about two element in one persName="alexander23"-->
        <p>I wanna key his car <format type="p">I want to get him back</format></p>
        <p>I wanna make him lunch <format type="p">But then I, I want to get him back;
            Woo</format></p>
        <p>I wanna <figlang type="meta">break his heart</figlang>
            <format type="p">But then I, I want to get him back; Yeah, you got it</format></p>
        <p>Then be the one to <figlang type="meta">stitch it up</figlang>
            <format type="p">But then I, I want to get him back; yeah</format></p>
        <p>Wanna kiss his face <format type="p">But then I, I want to get him back</format></p>
        <p>
            <figlang type="image">With an uppercut</figlang>
            <format type="p">But then I, I want to get him back</format>
        </p>
        <p>I wanna meet his mom <format type="p">But then I, I want to get him back</format></p>
        <p>Just to tell her her son sucks <format type="p">But then I, I want to get him
                back</format></p>
        <p>Oh, I wanna key his car, I wanna make him lunch <format type="p">But then I, I want to
                get him back; I want to</format></p>
        <p>I wanna <figlang type="meta">break his heart</figlang>, <figlang type="meta">stitch it
                right back up</figlang>
            <format type="p">But then I, I want to get him back; get him back</format></p>
        <p>
            <figlang type="image">I wanna kiss his face with an uppercut</figlang>
            <format type="p">But then I, I want to get him back; I want to</format>
        </p>
        <p>I wanna meet his mom, and tell her her son sucks, yeah <format type="p">But then I, I
                want to get him back; get him back</format></p>
    </bridge>

    <chorus rhyme="ababcaa">
        <p>I wanna get him back</p>
        <p>I wanna make him really jealous, wanna make him feel bad</p>
        <p>Oh, I wanna get him back</p>
        <p>'Cause then again, I really miss him, and it makes me real sad</p>
        <p>Oh, I want sweet revenge, and I want him again</p>
        <p>I want to get him back <format type="p">And then? And then</format></p>
        <p>I want to get him back, back, back</p>
    </chorus>

    <outro rhyme="aabcd">
        <p>I'll get him, I'll get him, I'll get him, I'll get him back (Woo-hoo)</p>
        <p>Get him back <format type="p">Come on, come on, woo</format></p>
        <p>I'm gonna get him so good, <figlang type="idiom">he's not even gonna know what hit
                him</figlang></p>
        <p>He's gonna love me and hate me at the same time</p>
        <p>
            <format type="p">Get him back, girl, you better get him back</format>
        </p>
        <p>
            <format type="p">You got it, got it</format>
        </p>
        <p>Oh, I don't know, I got him good, I got him really good</p>
    </outro>
</xml>
